so I was thinking about the brain
organoids you know the little tiny human
brains that we made from stem cells the
only thing that keeps them from actually
growing to the size of a baby brain is
that they don't have a vascular system
and then I wondered could it be used as
a treatment for ay so occasionally
babies are born without a brain they
have the brain stem they have the basic
reflexes needed to have a living body
but lack any form of brain structure now
we know that the brain Organo can
integrate with another brain like in the
experiment where they cut out a portion
of the mouse's brain and integrated the
brain organoid and it did the job of
that portion of the brain but when we
grew it near the decapitated body of a
mouse it actually made projections into
the spine and took over it controlled
the muscles so what would happen if we
took someone who was born without a
brain and then maybe lined the brain
cavity with brain organoids one or more
with a vascular system it should be able
to take over would it eventually become
functional they are essentially fetal
brains I think I'm going to write a
creepy pasta about this and submit it to
no sleep this week